Guide to the Larry Fagin Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
Larry Fagin papers
1956-2007
YCAL MSS 330
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
18.21
(19 boxes) + 1 film reel
The collection consists of material created and accumulated by Larry Fagin, stemming from his individual and collaborative work as a poet and editor, and, to a lesser extent, as a teacher, filmmaker, artist, choreographer, and journalist, and documenting his relationship with other poets and writers associated with the New York School. Material includes correspondence, printed material, typescripts of poems, essays, translations, and film scripts, publicity material for readings, lectures, and publications, interview transcripts, teaching files, collages, an 8 mm motion picture, and other material. The bulk of the collection consists of files compiled by Fagin according to correspondent and/or subject, including extensive files for Glen Baxter, Bill Berkson, Jack Collom, Clark Coolidge, Michael Friedman, John Godfrey, Naropa Institute, Ron Padgett, Poetry Project at St. Mark's, Judith Reifman, and Anne Waldman, among others.
Fagin, Larry, 1937-
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Purchased from Granary Books on the Edwin J. Beinecke Book Fund, 2008.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Access to original audiovisual recordings (Reel 714a) is restricted. Consult the Beinecke Library Access Services department for information about reference copies.
Larry Fagin
Larry Fagin was born in 1937, and graduated from the University of Maryland. He is the author or co-author of numerous collections of poetry, including Parade of the Caterpillars (1968), Brain Damage (1971), Two Serious Poems and One Other, with Bill Berkson (1971), Landscape, with George Schneeman (1972), The World of Leon, with Ron Padgett (1973), Rhymes of a Jerk (1974), Stabs (1979), Lime Rickeys, with Jack Collom (1994), and Dig & Delve, with Trevor Winkfield (1999). His poetry and prose have also appeared in magazines, such as Paris Review, Blue Suede Shoes, Poetry, Open Space, and Rolling Stone, as well as several anthologies of poetry.
Fagin published and edited Adventures in Poetry magazine (1968-1975) and Un Poco Loco, a monthly poetry newsletter (1978-1979). He was co-director of the Poetry Project at St. Mark's Church 1971 to 1976, and a founder and director of Danspace from 1975 to 1980. Since 1968, Fagin has taught creative writing to public school students and teachers. He was on the faculty at the Naropa Institute from 1977 to 1987, and chaired the Poetics Department from 1982 to 1984. He also taught at UCLA and New School University.
Scope and Contents
The collection consists of material created and accumulated by Larry Fagin, stemming from his individual and collaborative work as a poet and editor, and, to a lesser extent, as a teacher, filmmaker, artist, choreographer, and journalist, and documenting his relationship with other poets and writers associated with the New York School. Material includes correspondence, printed material, typescripts of poems, essays, translations, and film scripts, publicity material for readings, lectures, and publications, interview transcripts, teaching files, collages, an 8 mm motion picture, and other material. The bulk of the collection consists of files compiled by Fagin according to correspondent and/or subject, including extensive files for Glen Baxter, Bill Berkson, Jack Collom, Clark Coolidge, Michael Friedman, John Godfrey, Naropa Institute, Ron Padgett, Poetry Project at St. Mark's, Judith Reifman, and Anne Waldman, among others.
Arrangement
The collection is organized into three series: I. Correspondence and Subject Files, 1956-2007. II. Writings, 1956-2006. III. Professional Papers, 1968-2007.
American literature -- 20th Century; American poetry -- 20th Century; Authors, American -- 20th Century -- Archives; Poets, American -- 20th Century -- Archives; Motion pictures (visual works); Poets; Baxter, Glen, 1944-; Berkson, Bill, 1939-2016; Collom, Jack, 1931-2017; Coolidge, Clark, 1939-; Fagin, Larry, 1937-; Friedman, Michael, 1960-; Godfrey, John, 1945-; Padgett, Ron, 1942-; Reifman, Judith; Waldman, Anne, 1945-; Naropa Institute; St. Mark's Church In-the-Bowery (New York, N.Y.). Poetry Project
- Correspondence and Subject Files, 1956-2007; Series I; 14.5
  Arrangement
  Arranged alphabetically by surname of individual.
  - Acconci, Vito, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Adam, Helen, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Agis, Gaby, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Aldrich, Elizabeth, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Alexander, Paul, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Anagnopoulos, Kostas, circa 2003-2004 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Andre, Michael, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Andrews, Bruce, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Antin, Eleanor, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Arbolay, Dominick, 2001-2003 (Box 1, Folder 10-13)
  - Argeros, Gerad, undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Armantrout, Rae, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Arnold, Bill, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Aronowitz, Al, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Ashbery, John, 1970-2004 (Box 1, Folder 18-22)
  - Auster, Paul, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Balestri, Tetra, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Balken, Debra, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Ball, David, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Ballard, Micah, undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Banks, Russell, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Baraka, Amiri, circa 1980 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Baxter, Glen, 1970-2001 (Box 1, Folder 30-40)
  - Behrle, Jim, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Beltrametti, Franco, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Benson, Steve, 1979, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Berkson, Bill, 1975-2008 (Box 2, Folder 44-58)
  - Berkson, Lynn, 1974-1982 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Berkson, Moses, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Bernheimer, Alan, 1979-2006 (Box 2, Folder 61-62)
  - Bernstein, Charles, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Berrigan, Anselm, 2002-2007 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Berrigan, Ted, 1964-2000 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Berssenbrugge, Mei-Mei, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Biglieri, Gregg, 2003-2004 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Bishop, James, circa 1970 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Blackmer, Tracy, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Blaisdale, Gus, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Blaser, Robin, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Bloom, Euphrosyne, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Borgerson, Janet, 1989-2004 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Borregaard, Ebbe, undated (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Bouchard, Dan, undated (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Bouvier, Geoff, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Brainard, Joe, 1965-2004 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Brakhage, Stan, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Breeding, Leslie, undated (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Bremser, Ray, 1962-1977 (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - Brenner, Summer, 1994-2007 (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - Brodecky, Bill, 1959-2002 (Box 3, Folder 82-84)
  - Brodey, Jim, 1981-2001 (Box 3, Folder 85)
  - Brooker, Suzanne, undated (Box 3, Folder 86)
  - Brossard, Olivier, 2003-2007 (Box 3, Folder 87)
  - Brown, Lee Anne, 1987-2002 (Box 3, Folder 88)
  - Brown, Lewis, 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 89)
  - Brown, Rebecca, 1969-1979 (Box 3, Folder 90)
  - Brownstein, Michael, 1972-2007 (Box 3, Folder 91)
  - Bukowski, Charles, undated (Box 3, Folder 92)
  - Bunyard, Claudia, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 93)
  - Burch, Jennifer, 2003-2006 (Box 3, Folder 94)
  - Burckhardt, Rudy, 1977-2000 (Box 3, Folder 95)
  - Burger, Mary, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 96)
  - Burroughs, William, 1972-1983 (Box 3, Folder 97)
  - Bye, Reed, 1978-2003 (Box 3, Folder 98-99)
  - Cage, John, undated (Box 3, Folder 100)
  - Cameron, David, 2000-2002 (Box 3, Folder 101)
  - Card, Macgregor, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 102)
  - Carey, Steve, undated (Box 3, Folder 103)
  - Carlen, Fran, 2002-2007 (Box 3, Folder 104-105)
  - Carnevale, Chris, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 106)
  - Carroll, Bob, circa 1970 (Box 3, Folder 107)
  - Carroll, Jim, circa 1980 (Box 3, Folder 108)
  - Carroll, Paul, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 109)
  - Carter, Charlotte, undated (Box 3, Folder 110)
  - Cassidy, Daniel, undated (Box 3, Folder 111)
  - Ceravolo, Joe, 1970-2004 (Box 3, Folder 112)
  - Chaloner, David, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 113)
  - Chambers, Jack, 2004-2006 (Box 3, Folder 114)
  - Champion, Miles, 1998-2007 (Box 3, Folder 115-117)
  - Clark, Angelica, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 118)
  - Clark, Tom, 1969-1982 (Box 4, Folder 119)
  - Clay, Steve, 1998, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 120)
  - Codrescu, Andrei, 1970-1979 (Box 4, Folder 121)
  - Cohen, Ira, undated (Box 4, Folder 122)
  - Cohen, Keith, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 123)
  - Cohen, Marc, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 124)
  - Cohen, Scott, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 125)
  - Collins, Jess, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 126)
  - Collom, Jack, 1978-2007 (Box 4, Folder 127-133)
  - Collom, Jack & Hejinian, Lyn, 2006-2007 (Box 4, Folder 134-135)
  - Coolidge, Clark, 1973-2006 (Box 4, Folder 136-140)
  - Coolidge, Clark, 1973-2006 (Box 5, Folder 141-145)
  - Coolidge, Sylvia, circa 1989 (Box 5, Folder 146)
  - Corbett, Bill, 1998-2004 (Box 5, Folder 147)
  - Corso, Gregory, circa 1970-1982 (Box 5, Folder 148)
  - Cott, Jonathan, undated (Box 5, Folder 149)
  - Coultas, Brenda, undated (Box 5, Folder 150)
  - Creeley, Robert, 1999-2005 (Box 5, Folder 151)
  - Crozier, Andrew, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 152)
  - Culley, Peter, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 153)
  - Curtis, Jackie, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 154)
  - Dailey, Joel, 2001-2002 (Box 5, Folder 155)
  - Daley, Debora, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 156)
  - Davenport, Guy, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 157)
  - Davidson, Michael, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 158)
  - Davies, Alan, 1977-2003 (Box 5, Folder 159)
  - Davies, Kevin, 2000-2006 (Box 5, Folder 160-161)
  - Davis, Jordan, undated (Box 5, Folder 162)
  - Davis, Lydia, 2001-2006 (Box 5, Folder 163)
  - Davis, Tim, 1997-2006 (Box 5, Folder 164-165)
  - Day, Jean, 2004-2007 (Box 5, Folder 166)
  - Denby, Edwin, 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 167)
  - Dennis, Donna, undated (Box 5, Folder 168)
  - Dessner, Jessica, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 169)
  - Dickison, Steve, 2002-2007 (Box 5, Folder 170)
  - Didomenico, Rebecca, 1984-2003 (Box 5, Folder 171)
  - Diggory, Terry, 2004-2005 (Box 5, Folder 172)
  - Dilley, Barbara, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 173)
  - Dine, Jim, circa 1970 (Box 5, Folder 174)
  - DiPrima, Diane, circa 2003 (Box 5, Folder 175)
  - Dorn, Ed, undated (Box 5, Folder 176)
  - Dorsky, Nathanial, 1978-2007 (Box 5, Folder 177-178)
  - Dorward, Nate, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 179)
  - Druyan, Ann, 1974-1987 (Box 5, Folder 180)
  - Dull, Dora, circa 1965 (Box 5, Folder 181)
  - Duncan, Robert, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 182)
  - Dunn, Douglas, 1975-2005 (Box 6, Folder 183)
  - DuPlessis, Rachel Blau, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 184)
  - Durand, Marcella, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 185)
  - Dylan, Bob, undated (Box 6, Folder 186)
  - Edgar, Christopher, 1999-2004 (Box 6, Folder 187)
  - Edwards, Ernie, 2001-2003 (Box 6, Folder 188)
  - Eicher, Amanda, 2003-2004 (Box 6, Folder 189)
  - Ellingham, Lewis, 1983-1989 (Box 6, Folder 190)
  - Elliott, Richard, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 191)
  - Elmslie, Kenward, 1971-2001 (Box 6, Folder 192)
  - Elstein, Robert, 2002-2006 (Box 6, Folder 193)
  - Equi, Elaine, undated (Box 6, Folder 194)
  - Evans, Steve, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 195)
  - Fagin, Joan, 1970-1980 (Box 6, Folder 196)
  - Faville, Curtis, 1977, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 197)
  - Felver, Christopher, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 198)
  - Ferrari, Mary, 1977-2006 (Box 6, Folder 199-200)
  - Fields, Rick, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 201)
  - Finberg, Bonny, 2001-2003 (Box 6, Folder 202)
  - Flory, Michael, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 203)
  - Ford, Charles Henri, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 204)
  - Fox, Elizabeth, circa 1981 (Box 6, Folder 205)
  - Fox, Porter, 2005-2006 (Box 6, Folder 206)
  - Foye, Raymond, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 207)
  - Frank, Diane, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 208)
  - Freilicher, Jane, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 209)
  - Friedlander, Lee, circa 1983 (Box 6, Folder 210)
  - Friedman, Ed, 1980-2003 (Box 6, Folder 211)
  - Friedman, Michael, 1986-2007 (Box 6, Folder 212-217)
  - Fuchs, Alan, undated (Box 6, Folder 218)
  - Fund for NY Public Education, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 219)
  - Fyman, Cliff, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 220)
  - Gallup, Carol, undated (Box 7, Folder 221)
  - Gallup, Dick, 1966-2001 (Box 7, Folder 222)
  - Garden, Rebecca, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 223)
  - Gast, Tad, 1975-1980 (Box 7, Folder 224)
  - Gay, Reginald, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 225)
  - Gilbert, Alan, 2000-2001 (Box 7, Folder 226)
  - Gilfillan, Merrill, 1999-2003 (Box 7, Folder 227-228)
  - Ginsberg, Allen, 1956-1999 (Box 7, Folder 229)
  - Giorno, John, 1968-1987 (Box 7, Folder 230)
  - Gioseffi, Daniela, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 231)
  - Gitin, David, 1977,1979 (Box 7, Folder 232)
  - Giugliano, Luisa, 1997-2003 (Box 7, Folder 233)
  - Gizzi, Michael, 1990-2002 (Box 7, Folder 234)
  - Gizzi, Peter, 1993-1994 (Box 7, Folder 235)
  - Glickler, Paul, 1989-2003 (Box 7, Folder 236)
  - Godfrey, John, 1983-2003 (Box 7, Folder 237-240)
  - Golde, Morris, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 241)
  - Goldman, Judith, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 242)
  - Goldsmith, Kenneth, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 243)
  - Gottlieb, Michael, 1999, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 244)
  - Graybill, Jessie, 1999-2002 (Box 7, Folder 245)
  - Greene, Tinker, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 246)
  - Greenley, Emily, circa 2004 (Box 7, Folder 247)
  - Greenwald, Ted, 1970-1998 (Box 7, Folder 248)
  - Grooms, Red, undated (Box 7, Folder 249)
  - Gross, Mimi, 1977-1979 (Box 7, Folder 250)
  - Hall, Donald, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 251)
  - Hall, Steven, 1976-1998 (Box 7, Folder 252)
  - Hamilton, Alfred Starr, circa 1975 (Box 7, Folder 253-254)
  - Hanser, Carl, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 255)
  - Harris, Robert, 2001-2006 (Box 7, Folder 256-257)
  - Harrison, Julie, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 258)
  - Harrison, Lee, 1980-1994 (Box 7, Folder 259)
  - Harryman, Carla, 2001-2007 (Box 8, Folder 260-261)
  - Hartman, Yuki, circa 1997 (Box 8, Folder 262)
  - Harwood, Lee, undated (Box 8, Folder 263)
  - Hasegawa, Kreg, 2004-2006 (Box 8, Folder 264)
  - Heinowitz, Cole, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 265)
  - Hejinian, Lyn, 1980-2003 (Box 8, Folder 266)
  - Heliczer, Piero, circa 1981-1992 (Box 8, Folder 267)
  - Hell, Richard, 1991-2002 (Box 8, Folder 268)
  - Henderson, David, undated (Box 8, Folder 269)
  - Hennessy, Eileen, 1999-2003 (Box 8, Folder 270-272)
  - Henning, Barbara, undated (Box 8, Folder 273)
  - Herd, Dale, 1979-1982 (Box 8, Folder 274)
  - Hershon, Bob, undated (Box 8, Folder 275)
  - Highfill, Mitch, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 276)
  - Hiler, Jerome, 1987-2003 (Box 8, Folder 277)
  - Hiott, Andrea, circa 2002 (Box 8, Folder 278)
  - Hollo, Anselm, 1979-2001 (Box 8, Folder 279-280)
  - Holman, Bob, undated (Box 8, Folder 281)
  - Hopkins, John, 1981, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 282)
  - Hornick, Lita & Morton, undated (Box 8, Folder 283)
  - Horning, Ron, 1999-2003 (Box 8, Folder 284-286)
  - Howard, Peter, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 287)
  - Hoyem, Andrew, undated (Box 8, Folder 288)
  - Iljima, Brenda, 1999-2003 (Box 8, Folder 289)
  - Jacobs, Ken, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 290)
  - Jacquette, Yvonne, 1976, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 291)
  - Jarnot, Lisa, 1993-2003 (Box 8, Folder 292)
  - Johns, Jasper, undated (Box 8, Folder 293)
  - Johnston, Alastair, 1979-1988 (Box 8, Folder 294)
  - Jonas, Steve, undated (Box 8, Folder 295)
  - Jones, Kent, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 296)
  - Jordan, Larry, undated (Box 8, Folder 297)
  - Kane, Daniel, undated (Box 8, Folder 298)
  - Kashner, Sam, 1978-2003 (Box 8, Folder 299)
  - Katz, Alex, circa 1970 (Box 8, Folder 300)
  - Katz, Vincent, 1977-2003 (Box 8, Folder 301)
  - Kearney, Larry, 2000-2004 (Box 9, Folder 302-303)
  - Kerouac, Jack, 1986, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 304)
  - Killian, Kevin, 1964-2001 (Box 9, Folder 305)
  - Kim, Ann, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 306)
  - Kimball, George, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 307)
  - Kimberley, Nick, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 308)
  - King, Basil, 2004-2006 (Box 9, Folder 309)
  - King, Denyse, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 310)
  - King, Kenneth, 1977-1980 (Box 9, Folder 311)
  - Knott, Bill, undated (Box 9, Folder 312)
  - Knowles, Christopher, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 313)
  - Knowlton, Win, 1996, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 314)
  - Koch, Katherine, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 315)
  - Koch, Kenneth, 1987, undated (Box 9, Folder 316)
  - Kochan, Mushka, undated (Box 9, Folder 317)
  - Koehler, Michael, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 318)
  - Koestenbaum, Wayne, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 319)
  - Koethe, John, undated (Box 9, Folder 320)
  - Koller, James, undated (Box 9, Folder 321)
  - Kolmar, Richard, circa 2006 (Box 9, Folder 322)
  - Kolokithas, Dawn, 1985-1996 (Box 9, Folder 323)
  - Kornblum, Allan, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 324)
  - Kroebar, Theodora, undated (Box 9, Folder 325)
  - Kunin, Aaron, circa 2003 (Box 9, Folder 326)
  - Kupferberg, Tuli, circa 1962 (Box 9, Folder 327)
  - Kurz, Vivian, 1976-1990 (Box 9, Folder 328)
  - Kushner, Robert, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 329)
  - Kuykendall, Marc, 1999-2002 (Box 9, Folder 330-331)
  - Kyger, Joanne, 1978-2004 (Box 9, Folder 332)
  - Lacy, Steve, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 333)
  - Laird, Carobeth, undated (Box 9, Folder 334)
  - Lally, Michael, undated (Box 9, Folder 335)
  - Lange, Art, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 336)
  - Latta, John, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 337)
  - Lawton, Pamela, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 338)
  - Lee, Annabel, undated (Box 9, Folder 339)
  - Lehman, David, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 340)
  - Lenhart, Gary, 1989-2001 (Box 9, Folder 341)
  - Leslie, Frank, undated (Box 9, Folder 342)
  - Levine, Les, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 343)
  - Levine, Steve, undated (Box 9, Folder 344)
  - Levy, William, circa 1982-2004 (Box 9, Folder 345)
  - Lilien, Jadina, 1989-1990 (Box 9, Folder 346)
  - Lima, Frank, 1994, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 347)
  - Loewinsohn, Ron, undated (Box 9, Folder 348)
  - Lopate, Phillip, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 349)
  - Lowenstein, Tom, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 350)
  - Luster, Helen, circa 1983 (Box 9, Folder 351)
  - Lyons, Kim, undated (Box 9, Folder 352)
  - MacAdams, Lewis, 1977-1995 (Box 9, Folder 353)
  - MacAdams, Phoebe, 1976-1995 (Box 9, Folder 354)
  - MacInnis, Jamie, 1977-1980 (Box 9, Folder 355)
  - Magee, Mike, undated (Box 9, Folder 356)
  - Maier, Michael, undated (Box 9, Folder 357)
  - Mailer, Norman, 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 358)
  - Malanga, Gerard, 1970-1998 (Box 9, Folder 359)
  - Malmude, Stephen, 1976-1977, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 360)
  - Malone, Eric, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 361)
  - Marshall, Ed, undated (Box 9, Folder 362)
  - Martin, Richard, undated (Box 9, Folder 363)
  - Mathews, Harry, 1993-2003 (Box 9, Folder 364)
  - Mattingly, George, undated (Box 9, Folder 365)
  - Mattison, Christopher, 2002-2007 (Box 9, Folder 366-367)
  - Maunheimer, Sara, 1989-1999 (Box 10, Folder 368)
  - Mayer, Bernadette, 1970-1994 (Box 10, Folder 369-370)
  - Mayer, Emily, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 371)
  - McCain, Gillian, 1998-2006 (Box 10, Folder 372-374)
  - McClure, Michael, 2002-2004 (Box 10, Folder 375)
  - McEwen, Christian, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 376)
  - McKay, Nellie, circa 2005 (Box 10, Folder 377)
  - McNaughton, Duncan, 2003-2007 (Box 10, Folder 378)
  - Mead, Taylor, undated (Box 10, Folder 379)
  - Mednick, Murray, undated (Box 10, Folder 380)
  - Meltzer, David, 1977-2007 (Box 10, Folder 381-382)
  - Meltzer, Tina, 1987-1988 (Box 10, Folder 383)
  - Mesmer, Sharon, 1991-2006 (Box 10, Folder 384-385)
  - Messerli, Douglas, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 386)
  - Metcalf, Paul, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 387)
  - Mikolowski, Ken, 2007 (Box 10, Folder 388)
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 10, Folder 389)
  - Mlinko, Ange, 1997-2007 (Box 10, Folder 390-391)
  - Moore, Thurston, circa 2005 (Box 10, Folder 392)
  - Morgan, Bill, circa 2001 (Box 10, Folder 393)
  - Moriarty, Laura, undated (Box 10, Folder 394)
  - Moudry, Nick, circa 2002 (Box 10, Folder 395)
  - Moxley, Jennifer, 2001-2002 (Box 10, Folder 396)
  - Murphy, Ryan, 2003-2007 (Box 10, Folder 397)
  - Murray, Catherine, circa 1988 (Box 10, Folder 398)
  - Myles, Eileen, undated (Box 10, Folder 399)
  - Naropa Institute, 1977-2007 (Box 10, Folder 400-401)
  - Naropa Institute, 1977-2007 (Box 11, Folder 402-405)
  - Neufeld, Peter, 1996-2000 (Box 11, Folder 406)
  - Nguyen, Hoa, 1999-2000 (Box 11, Folder 407)
  - Niazmand, Mohammad Ali, circa 2006 (Box 11, Folder 408-409)
  - Nohejl, Daniel, undated (Box 11, Folder 410)
  - Nolan, Pat, circa 1977-1979 (Box 11, Folder 411)
  - North, Charles, 1974-2007 (Box 11, Folder 412-415)
  - Notley, Alice, circa 1977 (Box 11, Folder 416)
  - Obenzinger, Hilton, 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 417)
  - O'Brien, Linda, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 418)
  - O'Hara, Frank, circa 2000 (Box 11, Folder 419)
  - Oldenburg, Patty, undated (Box 11, Folder 420)
  - Olin, Jeni, undated (Box 11, Folder 421)
  - Olson, Charles, circa 1976 (Box 11, Folder 422)
  - Olson, Kirby, 1979-2000 (Box 11, Folder 423)
  - Owen, Maureen, circa 2001 (Box 11, Folder 424)
  - Padgett, Ron, 1969-2004 (Box 11, Folder 425-428)
  - Palmer, Michael, 1978-2003 (Box 11, Folder 429)
  - Park, Darragh, circa 1998 (Box 11, Folder 430)
  - Parnell, Kate, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 431)
  - Parsons, Clere, undated (Box 11, Folder 432)
  - Perreault, John, 1969-1971 (Box 11, Folder 433)
  - Perry, David, 1999-2007 (Box 12, Folder 434-435)
  - Persky, Stan, 1964-1965 (Box 12, Folder 436)
  - Pettet, Simon, 2007 (Box 12, Folder 437)
  - Phillips, Amber, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 438)
  - Pinney, Todd Allen, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 439)
  - Piper, Adrian, undated (Box 12, Folder 440)
  - Plymell, Charles, undated (Box 12, Folder 441)
  - Poetry Project at St. Mark's Church, 1972-1997 (Box 12, Folder 442-444)
  - Porter, Anne, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 445)
  - Possett, Benn, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 446)
  - Praed, Winthrop Mackworth, undated (Box 12, Folder 447)
  - Premper, Tobias, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 448)
  - Price, Laurie, 1987-1991 (Box 12, Folder 449)
  - Primack, Ronnie, undated (Box 12, Folder 450)
  - Prynne, J.H., 2003 (Box 12, Folder 451)
  - Randolph, Karin, circa 2007 (Box 12, Folder 452)
  - Ratcliff, Carter, undated (Box 12, Folder 453)
  - Reifman, Judith, 1987-1999 (Box 12, Folder 454-458)
  - Ricard, Rene, circa 1978 (Box 12, Folder 459)
  - Richie, Eugene, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 460)
  - Rivers, Sam, undated (Box 12, Folder 461)
  - Robbins, Jonathan, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 462)
  - Robinson, Edwin Arlington, undated (Box 12, Folder 463)
  - Robinson, Elizabeth, circa 2007 (Box 12, Folder 464)
  - Robinson, Kit, 1978-2007 (Box 12, Folder 465-466)
  - Robinson, Tracy, 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 467)
  - Rodefer, Stephen, 1978-1998 (Box 12, Folder 468)
  - Rohnert, Jan Volker, undated (Box 12, Folder 469)
  - Rosenberg, David, circa 2003 (Box 13, Folder 470)
  - Rosenstein, Jonathan, circa 1975 (Box 13, Folder 471)
  - Rossi, Emma, 2002-2007 (Box 13, Folder 472)
  - Rothenberg, Michael, 2004-2007 (Box 13, Folder 473)
  - Roundy, Richard, 2003-2007 (Box 13, Folder 474-475)
  - Ruff, Theo, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 476)
  - Ruscha, Ed, undated (Box 13, Folder 477)
  - St. Mark's Church, circa 1978 (Box 13, Folder 478)
  - Sanders, Ed, 1965-1978 (Box 13, Folder 479)
  - Saroyan, Aram, 1966-2006 (Box 13, Folder 480)
  - Savage, Tom, 1970-2005 (Box 13, Folder 481)
  - Scalapino, Leslie, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 482)
  - Schelling, Andrew, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 483)
  - Schjeldahl, Peter, circa 1969-1970 (Box 13, Folder 484)
  - Schlesinger, Kyle, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 485)
  - Schneeman, Carolee, circa 1996-1997 (Box 13, Folder 486)
  - Schneeman, Elio, undated (Box 13, Folder 487)
  - Schneeman, George, 1969-2002 (Box 13, Folder 488-489)
  - Schuyler, James, 1972-1977 (Box 13, Folder 490)
  - Segessman, Harry, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 491)
  - Senauke, Alan, undated (Box 13, Folder 492)
  - Sequin, Iliassa, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 493)
  - Serra, Richard, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 494)
  - Shapiro, David, 1979-1998 (Box 13, Folder 495)
  - Sharma, Prageeta, circa 1998 (Box 13, Folder 496)
  - Sheard, Sarah, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 497)
  - Shepard, Sam, undated (Box 13, Folder 498)
  - Sherry, James, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 499)
  - Siegal, Allan, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 500)
  - Silliman, Ron, 1977-2004 (Box 13, Folder 501)
  - Simas, Joseph, 1988-1990 (Box 13, Folder 502)